Guide to the Jesse Simons Papers WAG.044
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Jesse Simons Papers
1919-2000
WAG.044
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
12.0 linear feet in 12 record cartons
Jesse Simons (1917-2006) was a distinguished labor arbitrator, and served as Director of the American Artbitration Association’s Labor Management Institute. A veteran of the U.S. Trotskyist movement of the 1930s and 40s, he held a variety of blue-collar jobs, served in World War II, and became a union official and organizer. As an arbitrator he was called upon to rule on cases involving many important sectors of New York City labor, and served on the Personnel Review Board of the New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation and as an arbitrator for the National Mediation Board. The collection contains personal, political and professional correspondence, writings and presentations, arbitration and other decisions, reports and background files.
Simons, Jesse.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Donated by Jesse Simons in 1996. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 1996.005 and 1996.009. Additional materials were received in 1998, 2002 and 2005. The accession numbers NPA.2000.074 and NPA.2006.059 are also associated with this collection.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Born in New Haven in 1917, Jesse Simons had a long and distinguished career in labor arbitration. While director of the American Arbitration Association's Labor Management Institute, he helped to create the New York City Collective Bargaining Law. The law, enacted in 1967 under Mayor John V. Lindsay, soon led to the creation of the New York City Office of Collective Bargaining and set up procedures to mediate and arbitrate contract disputes between the city and the majority of its employees. The system remains in use to this day.
During Simons' early career in the 1930s and 40s, he held a variety of jobs including machinist, shipyard coppersmith and linotype operator. After attending the University of Minnesota and the University of Washington briefly, he became deeply involved in trade-union and Trotskyist politics in the Seattle area, and his interest in unions developed out of these political experiences. At various times he served as chief shop steward, educational director and executive board member of the International Association of Machinists, the International Union of Shipbuilding Workers of America and the United Electrical Workers. From 1944-1946 he served in the Army Air Force. Afterwards, he took a job as assistant to the political director of the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, doing publicity, lobbying and organizing union support for political candidates from 1948 to 1951. In 1954, he became manager of personnel and industrial relations for the New York Post. After leaving the Post in 1962, he directed the AAA's Labor Management Institute from 1963 to 1966. In 1966, he joined the United States Lines, becoming the company's vice president for labor relations from 1967 to 1970.
In the course of his work as an arbitrator, Simons worked with a wide range of unions and employers to resolve literally thousands of contract-related disputes. He became thoroughly conversant with working conditions and labor-management issues in every major sector of the New York City work force; he dealt with cases involving health care workers, transit workers, communications workers, service employees, electricians, teamsters, maritime workers, theatrical and television workers, garment workers and teachers, among others. He served on the Personnel Review Board of the New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation and dealt with railroad cases nationwide as an arbitrator for the National Mediation Board. One of his most widely publicized decisions was the award of a $440,000 salary to New York Yankees catcher Rick Cerone in 1981, rejecting the team offer of $350,000 made by owner George M. Steinbrenner III.
Simons traveled widely and pursued interests in art and archaeology, literature and music. Many in his circle of devoted friends came from these fields; there is evidence in the collection of his own experiments in poetry writing. His three marriages ended in divorce. He died in July 2006 in New York City.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains personal correspondence and biographical materials reflecting the wide range of Jesse Simons' cultural and intellectual interests. Professional correspondence found in this series relates to the major arenas of his activity as an arbitrator. Also included are articles and speeches by Simons and others, material documenting his work with the United States Lines, and industry reports and other background material related to his work. Of special interest is a file of political correspondence, 1945-1948. Written by Simons and signed "Buddy," these letters reflect his views and activities and as a member of the Workers Party, a Trotskyist group. The bulk of this collection is comprised of case files from arbitration decisions between the 1970s and 1990s, which represent the full subject range and geographical spread of Simons' work as an arbitrator. The majority of the decisions date from the 1980s.
Arrangement
Files are arranged alphabetically within series; groups of arbitration decisions are arranged by award or case number.
The collection is organized into two series:
Series I: Subject Files, 1945-2000
Series II: Arbitration Decisions, undated
American Arbitration Association.; United States Lines Company.; United States. National Mediation Board.; Workers Party (1940-1949); Agreements.; Arbitration and award |z United States.; Arbitration and award.; Arbitration decisions.; Arbitration, Industrial |z New York (State) |z New York.; Arbitration, Industrial |z United States.; Articles.; Correspondence.; Grievance arbitration.; Labor Unions |z United States |y 1980-1990.; New York (N.Y.); Photographs.; Reports.
- Series I: Subject Files, 1919-2000
  - Agents Committee: Statement of Position, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aiken, Conrad, undated, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholism, Drug Abuse and Excessive Absences: Simons Article (NYU 32nd Annual National Conference on Labor), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association (AAA): Conference and Materials re: Newspaper Industry, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AAA: Labor Management Institute (LMI), 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AAA/LMI: Simons Articles for AAA Journal, 1994, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AAA/LMI: Simons Article re:, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AAA/LMI: Labor-Management Conferences, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AAA/LMI: New York City Collective Bargaining Law, Appendix Materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AAA/LMI: NYC Collective Bargaining Law, Correspondence, Drafts, Speeches, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AAA/LMI: NYC Collective Bargaining Law: Preliminary Report, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AAA/LMI: NYC Collective Bargaining Law, 25th Anniversary, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The American City and its Public Employee Unions: Simons Paper for Industrial Relations Research Assn. Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Radio Association: Contract Proposals, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Radio Association: Statement of Position, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Amtrak Disciplinary Procedures: Simons Testimony before U.S. House of Representatives, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration of Unmeritorious Grievances: Simons article, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Arbitrator's Remedial Powers Revisited: Simons article for National Academy of Arbitrators, 43rd Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board of Inquiry: Maritime Industry Reports, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Inquiry: West Coast Maritime Industry Reports, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bogus: Article and Research Materials (printing trades), undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Case Study... Maritime Industry-1965 by Lee Pressman (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Catherwood Library, Cornell University, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - A Century of American Reform-Cause for Optimism: Simons Article, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cerone, Rick: Arbitration (Baseball), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cerone, Rick: Arbitrarion (Baseball) (Graphic), 1981 (Box MSOS004, Folder 1)
  - Cole, David L.: Preface to Frontiers of Collective Bargaining, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Collective Bargaining; Simons Article, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Collective Bargaining: Simons Article for Industrial Bulletin, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Collective Bargaining: Simons Article for Ditchley Conference, UK, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Comments on Arbitration: Simons Article, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "Computer's Effects on Collective Bargaining": Simons Article, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cook, Alice: Articles in Industrial Relations, 1966, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Cool is the Young Liberal: The Cool Young Liberal: Simons Article, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1970's (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Employee Loyalty Obligations: Session at AAA Arbitration Day, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Esso Petroleum: Simons Report re: Marketing Dept., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Freedom of Information Act: Request and Documents (re: JS), undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Greenberg, Noah: Simons Interview about (transcript and published version), 1993, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Industry Arbitration: Simons article, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Impact of Maritime Collective Bargaining on the Maritime Industry: American Merchant Marine Inst., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Relations Course, Yale School of Organization and Management: Simons, Guest Lecturer, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - International Association of Masters, Mates and Pilots: Statement by President Charles M. Crooks, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Jacob K. Javits Center: Arbitration, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (MEBA): Statements and Agreements, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Maritime Labor Relations: Bargaining Restructure, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Labor Relations: Warner-Healy Study for the Maritime Administration, U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Maritime Strike, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - National Academy of Arbitration: Simons Speech, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - National Mediation Board: Railroads, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - National Mediation Board: Railroads (Conference), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19A)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board: Critique, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New York City Collective Bargaining Law: Photographs, Apr 1, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21A)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (NYCHHC), 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NYCHHC: Clippings, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NYCHHC: Helen Bryant Case, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYCHHC: Patient Abuse Grievances, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NYCHHC: Personnel Review Board (PRB), 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NYCHHC: PRB, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NYCHHC: PRB, undated, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYCHHC: PRB Accountability Procedures, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYC Office of Collective Bargaining: Annual Reports, 1968, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NYC Office of Collective Bargaining: Arvid Anderson Article, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NYC Office of Collective Bargaining: Philip J. Ruffo Reports, 1972-1973, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New York State Nurses Association, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Past Practice Revisited -- An Attempt at Codification: Simons Article, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Patient Abuse: Arbitration (reports, working papers, correspondence, etc.), 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Personal Documents, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Board of Inquiry: Maritime Dispute, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Labor-Management Conference on Grievance-handling and Arbitration: Simons on Neutral's Responsibilities, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Report on Collective Bargaining.. .in the Maritime Industry (Simons, author), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Resumes (Simons), undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Scheftel, Stuart: NYC Mayoral Campaign, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Seafarers International Union: Memorandum of Agreement, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Simons, Jesse: Clippings, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Simons, Jesse: Portraits, 1919-1967, undated (Box 3, Folder 19A)
  - Stone, Moe: Simons Speech, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Tamiment Library: Correspondence re: Max Shachtman Papers, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tanker Labor Service Committee, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - United States Lines: Confidential Memoranda, Feb 1967-Nov 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - United States Lines: Confidential Memoranda, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - United States Lines: Confidential Memoranda, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - United States Lines: Confidential Memoranda, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - United States Lines: Correspondence and Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - United States Lines: Simons Departure from…, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - United States Lines: Simons Speech, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Work Rules, Featherbedding and Automation: Article, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Writings: Speeches and Notes, Political, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Series II: Arbitration Decisions, undated
  - Actors' Equity Association v. League of Resident Theatres, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Air Micronesia v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Akron Faculty Association v. Akron Central School District, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen and Affiliated Crafts of North America, Local 1 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees, Local 342 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Food Store Employees Union, Local 464 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Government Employees v. U.S. Coast Guard Support Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Government Employees, Local 1760 v. Social Security Administration (2 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Government Employees, Local 1917 v. U.S. Department of Justice, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Government Employees, Local 3692 v. Veterans Administration, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Musicians v. Ice Capades Inc., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), D.C. #37 v. American Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1306 v. American Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1559 v. American Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1549 v. City of New York Department of Sanitation, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1549 v. City of New York Human Resources Administration, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 384 v. CUNY, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1597 v. CUNY, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37 v. Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37 v. New York Public Library (3 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 82 v. New York State Department of Correctional Services (3 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37 v. Office of Municipal Labor Relations, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME, Local 374 v. Queens Botanical Garden Society, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1321 v. Queensborough Public Library (3 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME, Council 4 v. State of Connecticut, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - AFSCME, Council 4 v. State of Connecticut, Commission on the Deaf and Hearing Impaired (2 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME, Council 4 v. State of Conn., Department of Children and Youth Services (2 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - AFSCME v. State of Conn., Department of Human Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - AFSCME, Council 4 v. State of Conn., Department of Income Maintenance, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - AFSCME, Council 4 v. State of Conn., Department of Motor Vehicles, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - AFSCME v. State of Conn., Division of Children and Protective Services, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - AFSCME, Council 4, Local 749 v. State of Conn., Judicial Department (6 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - AFSCME, D.C. 37, Local 1931 v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (3 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Alvarez, Anthony v. Trans World Airlines, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists v. NYC Opera, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists v. A/A Inc., undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - American Postal Workers Union v. United States Postal Service (7 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - American Train Dispatchers Association v. Penn Central Transportation Co., undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Workers International v. Nabisco, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Bethpage Congress of Teachers v. Bethpage Board of Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Board of Education of Vocational Schools of Bergen, NJ v. Bergen City Vocational Technical Education Association, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Brewery Delivery Co. v. Brewers Board of Trade, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Brotherhood of Security Personnel, Officers, and Guards v. Montifiore Hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Brotherhood of Security Personnel, Officers, and Guards v. Mt. Sinai Hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Buffalo Newspaper Guild v. Buffalo Courier-Express, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association v. City of Buffalo, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Building Service Employees International Union, Locals 32B and 32J v. Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, undated (Box 4, Folder 46a)
  - Burns International Security Services v. International Union, United Plant Guard Workers of America, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Carborundum Co. v. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Carrell, Candace v. Empire Blue Cross/Blue Shield, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - City Employees Union v. NYC Housing Authority, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. County of Westchester, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. State of NY Department of Corrections, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. State of NY Department of Mental Hygiene (11 cases), undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. State of NY Department of Social Services, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. State of NY Drug Abuse Control Services, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Civil Service Employees Association v. State of NY Executive Branch, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Clarkstown Teachers Association v. Clarkstown Board of Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Communication Workers of America (CWA) et al. v. New York Telephone Co. and American Arbitration Assn., undated (Box 4, Folder 57A)
  - CWA, Local 1301 v. NYNEX Information Resources Co. (1 of 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - CWA, Local 1301 v. NYNEX Information Resources Co. (2 of 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - CWA, Local 1101 v. NY Telephone Co. (4 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CWA v. Southern Central Bell Telephone Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CWA v. Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CWA, Local 1072 v. Teleprompter Corp., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Employees Union v. State of CT Department of Transportation (2 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Employees Union v. State of CT Mental Health Center, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Container Corp. of America v. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 609, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correction Officers Benevolent Association (COBA) v. City of NY Department of Corrections (1 of 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - COBA v. City of NY Department of Corrections (2 of 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - COBA of Orange County v. County of Orange, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Cran, Patricia v. Trans World Airlines, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Curick, Lorraine v. Trans World Airlines, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Department of Health and Human Services v. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 3369 (2 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Directors Guild of America v. Columbia Broadcasting System, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Distributive Workers of America v. Glemby Company, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Distributive Workers of America v. La Salle Letter Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Distributive Workers of America v. St. John's Associates (2 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Distributive Workers of America v. Speed-O-Lite Corp., undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - District #65 UAW v. Niebart Association, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - District #1199 Hospital Workers v. Syosset Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - District #1199 Hospital Workers - R.N. Division v. United Odd Fellows, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Doctor's Council v. Greenspan, Robert, DDS, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199 v. Flower Fifth Ave Hospital (2 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199 v. Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199 v. League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199 v. NY Medical College, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199 v. St. Barnabas Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Eastchester Teachers' Association v. Board of Education of Eastchester, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ellin, Mark v. Health and Security Plan, AFSCME, DC 37, undated (Box 5, Folder 28a)
  - Employees' Union of Purolator v. Purolator, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Employer Trustees of the Newspaper Guild of NY v. Guild of Trustees of Newspaper Guild of NY, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Esposito, Rosemarie v. Phelps Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Association of Monroe Community College v. Monroe Community College, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Federal Employees Metal Trades Council v. Portsmouth Naval Shipyard, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Federal Plant Quarantine Inspectors' National Association v. US Department of Agriculture, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Fire Department Dispatchers Benevolent Association v. the City of New York and NYC Fire Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)